

Stuart Broady A Professional Web & Graphic Designer

CONTACTME

Phone Number:

+0 012 3456789

Fmail¹

youremailhere@gmail.com

Website:

www.yourwebsitehere.com

Address:

123-C, Downtown Road, New York, United States.

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe XD

Indesigr

Figma

Sketch

INTERESTS

Travelino

Snooker

Video Games

Photography

Book Reading

PROFILE

Reliable, qualified, and experienced graphic designer working mainly in the IT industry, particularly in software houses. Excellence in creativity, problem-solving, time-management, and technical skills. Offering industrial exposure and providing design solutions for a broad range of webmasters and app developers. Works well with the team of graphic designers, and highly participative in business meetings.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer (2016 - 2020)

I Led a team that focused on providing designs to e-commerce websites. Completed most orders in a 6-month period and won the perfect designer award.

Web Designer (2014 - 2016)

I worked on testing and improving their websites' designs. Worked with different content management systems and prepared plans for website structure and design.

UI / UX Designer (2012 - 2014)

I created original graphic designs, including images, sketches, and tables. I've built page navigation buttons and search fields.

EDUCATION

Masters in Information Technology (2012 - 2014)

The field of my research in the post-graduation degree was "The role of the efficient interface in medical applications."

Bachelors in Computer Science (2010 - 2012)

I had 4.0 CGPA in my undergraduate degree. My project got the first position at the international level that helped me won a gold medal.